raing sea creatures for absolutely no
reason also I do not like the ocean
inspired by this absolute nightmare of a
video sent to me by a friend of this
Engler fish and this disgusting Goblin
is reaching near the surface of the
ocean which violates the long-standing
agreement we have with deep sea
creatures that they stay far enough
below the surface that we can pretend
they don't exist zero out of 10 this is
a bat fish and I think it's adorable I
would probably kiss this fish on the
lips 10 out of 10 and his back fins look
like legs close the ocean immediately
shut it down this is a filter mouth
shark and I want this image scrubbed
from the internet and also from my brain
I truly don't understand people who swim
with these creatures and it is your
prerogative to do so but if I were in
the ocean and this confronted me I would
need several adults I would be
inconsolable you would probably have to
put me in a hospital also it looks like
this when its mouth is closed and its
eye and it's no all of it is bad
negative 100 out of 10 this is a
flapjack octopus which is shockingly
hard to say it's adorable whatever these
little things are that look like ears 1
million out of 10 it looks like a living
stress ball this fish is called a
northern stargazer which sounds like it
should be beautiful but instead it looks
like this if I was on a beach and I saw
this fish I would punch it directly in
the face directly this is a red handfish
and not only is he adorably grouchy he
looks like he was making out with Taylor
Swift at a Grammy's Afterparty look at
his stupid little fin hands I like him8
out of 10 this is called like a Wong or
something I do not like when a creature
imitates surface like if I'm in the
ocean which I am not and I step on
something that I think is ground but
it's alive I'm calling the cops I don't
like it zero out of 10 I swear to God
y'all has anybody like checked on the
ocean is she going through some stuff
this is a telescope fish and honestly
throw the whole thing in the trash start
over you what I don't want this to live
on the same Earth that I'm on in any
capacity does it not look embarrassed to
be here like did they put a mirror in
front of this fish in this and the fish
was like you've got to be kidding me
that's what I look like why are there so
many ocean creatures that look like
they're partially finished this looks
like like a papier-mâché project that
somebody started and 70% through was
like this actually sucks and it actually
does suck this is a goblin shark see it
didn't even get an upper lip I don't
know what there's so much extra material
for this to be bare yuck Zer out of 10
this is an orish and if I were submerged
in the ocean in this surface I would
need to be evacuated from Earth you
could shoot me from a cannon into outer
space if an image ever surfaces of me in
the ocean next to a creature that is
multiple times larger than my own body
body it's doctored or it's against my
will I'm being coerced
because there's no way also this looks
like a giant idiot minnow that you're in
like Honey I Shrunk the Kids doesn't it
like this if this is minnow size I'm
good if this is the size of like a Volvo
pass obviously zero out of 10